fireeye.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy and Cookie Policy | FireEye

## FireEye Online Privacy Statement

FireEye respects your privacy. When using our website, you may get information, communicate with us, or link to other websites with whom we do business. While doing this, you may give us information so that we can provide enhanced products or services to you, as well as personalize your experience on our Website. This online privacy policy describes how FireEye and its affiliates and subsidiaries use and protect Personal Information that you share with us. "Personal Information" is information that enables us to identify you. Examples of this kind of information include your email address, name, title, or mailing address, and there are other similar kinds of information that may be used for the same purpose.

Your privacy, and the privacy of all users of www.fireeye.com, is of the highest priority. If you have any questions, please email us. We will not knowingly collect or use Personal Information as defined by law without parental consent.

This policy governs websites owned and operated by FireEye. Our policy does not govern websites of other parties to which we may provide links because FireEye is not responsible for, and cannot control the privacy practices or content of, those sites.

Here are the principles governing our information practices and other privacy aspects of our websites:

  * Information Collection and Use
  * Information Sharing and Disclosure
  * Cross-border transfer
  * Questions or Suggestions
  * IP Information Collection and Use Practices
  * Cookies
  * Data Storage
  * Contact Us

#### Information Collection and Use

  * FireEye collects Personal Information when you register for FireEye information such as whitepapers and reports, newsletters or webcasts, visit FireEye pages, and enter promotions.
  * FireEye also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, FireEye cookie information, and the page(s) you requested.
  * FireEye may collect any additional information relating to you that you voluntarily provide to us directly through our websites or indirectly through our representatives or business partners.
  * FireEye may use Personal information received from you in connection with: to fulfill your requests for information on products and services or any specific questions sent to us, to respond to any complaints, to contact you about offers and new products, to follow up on marketing initiatives and to generally manage your relationship with us.

#### Information Sharing and Disclosure

  * FireEye will not sell or rent your Personal Information to anyone.
  * FireEye will send Personal Information about you to other companies or people when:
    * We have your consent to share the information;
    * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;
    * We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of FireEye (e.g. affiliates, distributors or resellers) to provide a product or service to you or for further follow-up related to your interests.
    * We have to disclose your Personal Information in respond to a lawful request by public authorities and agencies, to meet any applicable law and regulation or to protect FireEye’s assets as permitted by law.
    * We are subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC). We may be required to disclose personal information that we handle under the Privacy Shield in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

#### Cross-Border Transfer

  * FireEye complies with the requirements of the U.S.-EU [Privacy Shield Framework](https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome), as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. FireEye adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity and purpose limitation, access and recourse, enforcement and liability with respect to all personal information transferred from the EU or Switzerland to the US within the scope of its Privacy Shield certification. If there is any conflict between the terms in this Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/list>.
  * FireEye remains to adhere to the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S. - Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce, which will not be affected by the participation in the Privacy Shield Framework.
  * Certain personal information may be subject to more specific privacy policies of FireEye, which are also consistent with the requirements of the U.S.-EU [Privacy Shield Framework.](https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome)
  * Unless we tell you differently, companies who work on behalf of FireEye do not have any right to use the Personal Information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us. FireEye ensures that those companies are contractually bound to confidentiality and use the data received on behalf of FireEye in line with this Policy and guarantee an adequate level of data protection. FireEye we will remain liable for any failure by the third party that receives personal information on behalf of FireEye, unless we prove that the event giving rise to the damage was solely caused by the third party.

#### Access to Information

FireEye strives to keep your Personal information accurate and up to date. You may request to review, correct or modify and delete the Personal Information that you have previously provided to us, or object to the use or processing of such Personal Information by us. In such cases, please send us the respective request to [privacy@fireeye.com](mailto:privacy@fireeye.com) and we will respond to your requests within 30 days.

#### IP Information Collection and Use Practices

  * FireEye receives IP addresses from all users because this information is automatically reported by your browser each time you view a Web page.
  * When a FireEye Web page is requested and viewed, that request is logged on our servers with information including the IP address of the computer that requested the page.
  * IP addresses may be used for various purposes, including estimating the total number of users visiting FireEye from specific countries or regions of the world.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a website's computers and is stored on your computer's hard drive.

Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but to protect your privacy, your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

_FireEye Practices Regarding Cookies_   
FireEye uses cookies for a number of purposes, including to:

  * Provide you with customized content.
  * Keep track of preferences you specify while you are using FireEye's products and services.
  * Estimate and report our total audience size and traffic.
  * Conduct research to improve FireEye content and services.
  * Require you to reenter your FireEye password after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you.

In addition to the first-party cookies we set, we use external services that set third-party cookies to:

  * Enable information sharing across social media services.
  * Provide you with targeted advertising in relevant contexts on external sites.
  * Keep track of preferences you specify while you are using third-party services.
  * Enable third parties to aggregate anonymous user behavior data and provide such research data to FireEye.
  * Monitor and report on site and service usage across FireEye websites.
  * Query third-party services such as Twitter for recently changed information.

_Similar Technologies We Use_   
In addition to cookies, we use Web beacons (also known as "clear GIFs" and "1x1" pixels) and coded URLs. These techniques may be used:

  * In online advertising to determine which advertisements you have viewed.
  * In our promotional emails to track whether an email has been viewed and subsequent clicks on hyperlinks.
  * To support remarketing for AdWords Ads on the Google Display Network. Remarketing technology serves you ads across multiple websites based on your browsing interest and behavior.

To opt out of Web beacon tracking, choose "DECLINE" on the FireEye Cookie Preferences control at the bottom of this page. Note that this will disable all first-party cookie sources from www.fireeye.com. In addition, you may choose not to open emails or download images in emails you receive from FireEye.

To opt out of tracking via coded URLs, you may choose not to click on hyperlinks embedded in marketing emails you receive from FireEye.

_Cookies in Use on FireEye Websites_

Type of Cookies | Source | Where Used | Take Control  
---|---|---|---  
Strictly Necessary | First party | **csportal.fireeye.com** | As these cookies are required for proper functioning of the support portal, there are no controls to disable them.

You may block them with your browser, but support portal functionality may become impaired.  
  
Performance | First party | **www.fireeye.com**

**www2.fireeye.com**

| 

The first party cookies are used to measure site usage and evaluate site performance. We aggregate the information provided by the cookies to provide summary metrics. No personally identifiable information is collected or stored.

The third-party cookies are used to support marketing activities both on the FireEye site and on third-party sites, and may collect personally identifiable information.

Control via your browser:

Control via Third-Party Sites:

Control via the FireEye Cookie Preferences Control:

Third party | **www.fireeye.com**

**www2.fireeye.com**

**blog.fireeye.com**

**newton.newtonsoftware.com**  
  
Functionality | First party | **www.fireeye.com** | 

The first-party cookies are used to enable you to interact with our social media sites.

The third-party cookies are used to support marketing activities both on the FireEye site and on third-party sites, and may collect personally identifiable information. Third-party cookies are also used to remember your information for the purpose of pre-populating forms, and to enable you to interact with our social media sites.

Control via your browser:

Control via Third-Party Sites:

Third party | **www.fireeye.com**

**www2.fireeye.com**

**blog.fireeye.com**

**newton.newtonsoftware.com**  
  
Targeting or Advertising | First party | **blog.fireeye.com** | 

The first-party cookies are used to measure site usage and evaluate site performance. We aggregate the information provided by the cookies to provide summary metrics. No personally identifiable information is collected. Activity information is stored to enable historical reporting.

The third-party cookies collect personally identifiable information used to support marketing activities both on the FireEye site and on third-party sites. Some of the third-party cookies support the delivery of interest-based advertising on sites unrelated to FireEye (remarketing). Third-party cookies are also used to remember your information for the purpose of pre-populating forms, interacting with our Careers service provider site, and to enable you to interact with our social media sites.

Control via your browser:

Control via Third-Party Sites:

Control via the FireEye Cookie Preferences Control:

Third party | **www.fireeye.com**

**blog.fireeye.com**

**newton.newtonsoftware.com**  
  
_FireEye's Sites_   

  * **www.fireeye.com** \- corporate website
  * **www2.fireeye.com** \- marketing services hosted by Marketo
  * ****blog.fireeye.com**** \- corporate blog
  * **newton.newtonsoftware.com** \- careers area services, including presenting job openings and receiving resume submissions
  * **csportal.fireeye.com** \- customer support portal

_Choices About Cookies_   
You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. This site provides instructions for adjusting cookie preferences for common browsers:

If your browser is not listed on the site above, check your browser's "Help" menu to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

**Controlling Cookies via Third-Party Opt-in/Opt-out Websites**

These sites enable you to manage opt-in and opt-out preferences for multiple cookies via a consolidated UI or individual "op-out" cookies. This is a convenient alternative to controlling cookies individually.

  * <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>
  * <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>

**Controlling Cookies via the FireEye Cookie Preferences Control**

FireEye provides a control that allows you to disable first-party cookies and Web beacon tracking on www.fireeye.com. The control has two settings:

  * ACCEPT: With this setting, all cookies and Web beacons are delivered normally.
  * DECLINE: With this setting, first-party cookies and Web beacons are not delivered from www.fireeye.com.

FireEye has multiple websites comprising its web presence, and the Cookie Preferences Control only affects first-party cookies and Web beacons sourced from www.fireeye.com.

  * When you transition to other sites, this privacy policy no longer applies, and the privacy policy of the other sites come into effect.
  * When browsing a site other than www.fireeye.com, FireEye recommends that you check the privacy policy local to that site to determine how it might affect you.

Note: The FireEye Cookie Preferences Control setting is specific to the web browser used to adjust the setting. If you browse the www.fireeye.com site using a different web browser application, or a different device, you will need to select your preferred setting again.

#### Data Storage and Security

_Account Information_

  * When you submit information to FireEye, a temporary copy of that information is routinely made to prevent accidental loss of your information through a computer malfunction or human error.
  * Please note that any information that we have copied may remain in back-up storage for some period of time after your deletion request. This may be the case even though no information about your account remains in our active user databases.

_Servers_

  * The FireEye computers (called "servers") that send your Web pages process and store an enormous amount of information every day. These computer records are called "log files."
  * Log files are used for analysis, research, auditing, and other purposes, as described above. After this information has been used, it is stored and is inaccessible. Until the information is stored, your FireEye ID may remain in our active server log files.

_Security_

  * Appropriate technical and physical safeguard measures are in place to protect against unauthorized or unlawful access, misuse, accidental loss, destruction and alternation of any Personal Information which are shared with us in the course of using our website services.

#### Dispute Resolution

  * If you believe your Personal Information has been used in a way that is not consistent with this Policy, we invite you to contact FireEye first under [privacy@fireeye.com](mailto:privacy@fireeye.com). We will make all efforts to resolve your complaints timely and accurately. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S. based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.
  * Further, FireEye has committed to cooperate with EU Data Protection Authorities (DPAs) and to comply with the information and advice provided to it by an informal panel of DPAs in relation to such unresolved complaints as determined by the Privacy Shield Principles.
  * Under certain conditions, EU individuals may seek redress from the Privacy Shield Panel, a binding arbitration mechanism.

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, [please contact us](http://www.fireeye.com/company/contact.html).

#### Policy Updates

We may update our Policy from time to time. We will post the updated version in this section of the website. If the revision is significant and may materially change our data privacy practices , we will notify you by using other means, e.g. via email. We will also keep prior versions of this Policy in an archive for your review (see Change History).

Last Updated: September 23rd, 2016

Download .pdf version

Change History
